Finding Aid for the Jesse Ely Wills Papers
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Re-ED paper (revision of 5-1-5-79) (Booklet) Project Re-ED: New Concepts for Helping Emotionally Disturbed Children - Evaluation by a Panel of Visitors with a Foreward by Nicholas Hobbs (Box 78)
- Papers of Bill Lewis
- Re-ED original (5-29-79) (Box 78)
- Re-ED paper Blue edition: re-ED paper (Box 78)
- "Helping Disturbed Children: Psychological and Ecological Strategies, II; Project Re-ED, Twenty Years Later," by Nicholas Hobbs (final correction copy, 6-28-79, master) (Box 78)
- Re-ED paper (Box 78)
- Pamphlets, brochures, booklets (Box 79)
- Cassette tape entitled "Wheeler on Re-ED" (Box 79)
- Folders of notes
- File Key, Provost's Office (Box 80)
- 14 Mr. Hobbs, Personal (A - H) (Box 80, Folder 14)
- 14 Mr. Hobbs, Personal (I - Z) (Box 80, Folder 14)
- Mr. Hobbs, Personal: University of Texas (Box 80, Folder 14.012)
- Center for Advanced Study in the Behavioral Sciences (Box 80, Folder 14.013)
- Future Commitments (Box 80, Folder 14.014)
- Mr. Hobbs, Personal: TIAA Information, etc. (Box 80, Folder 14.02)
- Book Orders, Nicholas Hobbs (Box 80, Folder 14.2)
- Mr. Hobbs. Personal: Personal Forms and Information (Box 80, Folder 14.03)
- Mr. Hobbs, Personal: Family Correspondence (Box 80, Folder 14.05)
- Mr. Hobbs, Personal: Maps (Box 80, Folder 14.06)
- Veteran Administration - Notification of Personnel Action (Box 80, Folder 14.08)
- Mr. Hobbs, Personal: Letters of Congratulations (Box 80, Folder 14.09)
- Mr. Hobbs, Personal: Moscow Trip (Box 80, Folder 14.011)
- Mr. Hobbs, Round Table (Box 80, Folder 14.201)
- 2 President Claunch (1967) (Box 80, Folder 2)
- 2 President Claunch (1969) (Box 80, Folder 2)
- 2 President Claunch (1968) (Box 80, Folder 2)
- Hobbs Reading File (1975) (Box 80)
- Hobbs Reading File (1973) (Box 80)
- "Action Sociale Discours et Realite Perspectives," Hommage au Professor Robert LaFon; Journees nationales. de l'A.C. T. I.F. (1980) [Lea Dossiers De L'A.C.T.I.F. 03] (Box 81)
- History of Sauvegarde De L'Enfance Et De L' Adolescence par R. LaFon (Box 81)
- Intelligence Paper - Background Papers (Box 81)
- Intelligence Paper (Booklet) Early Adolescence: Perspectives and Recommendations, prepared for the National Science Foundation (9-78) (Box 81)
- "How to Change the Process of Teaching Basic Reading Skills in Secondary Schools," by Jane Stallings (5-79) (Box 81)
- Chapter 1- "Constancy and Change: A View of the Issues," by Orville G. Brim, Jr. and Jerome Kagan (final revised copy; 5-79) (Box 81)
- Survey of Basic Skills Programs for Adolescents in Seven States, from SRI International Educational Policy Research Center (5-77) (Box 81)
- AAAS Paper
- Haywood's Comments (Box 81)
- Stipek
- AAAS Paper, background papers (2 folders) (Box 81)
- Minutes of Staff Meetings (9-19-61; 12-21-64) (Box 82)
- Education 282M - Methods of Counseling (Spring, 1947) (Box 82)
- Draft of the Report of the Project on Classification of Exceptional Children (9-1-73) (Box 82)
- Recordings of Group Therapy (5 plastic discs inside cover of black book entitled Group Therapy) (Box 82)
- The Role of the Leader in Nondirective Group Psychotherapy -- (carbon copy) (Box 82)
- (Master's Thesis) The Effect of Manifest Anxiety Upon Incidental and New Task Learning by Mary Irene Duwall (August, 1956) (Box 82)
- Incomplete Sentences
- Readaptation (Decembre1 1968; Septembre-Octobre, 1976) (Master's Thesis) A Study of Two Predictors of Academic Success of Foreign Students at Peabody College by Akira Kobasigawa (August, 1956) (Box 82)
- Esprit, Nouvelle Serie, L'Enfance Randicapee (Novembre, 1965) (Box 82)
- Guide des parents d'enfants inadaptes (handicapes mentaux) et de leurs ~par Michel Leibovici (1973) (Box 82)
- L' Action Familiale Dans Lea Associations de Parents Et Am.is D""Enfants InadapteS (1974) - (Box 82)
- Bibliographic Sur Lea Problemes De Deficience Mentale (Folder) UNAPEI - Union Nationale des Associations De Parents (Box 82)
- D'Enfants Inadaptes (Box 82)
- Mental Deficiency Research Data Cards (6-26-81) (Box 83)
- Miscellaneous unidentified rel-to-reel tapes (Box 84)